Scroll down my feed, it's a circus everyday.
Opinions over evidence, no one cares what experts say.
Shouting matches everywhere, sensory quakes, quack, bry.
Collusion's a currency, logic's genocide.
We've all suspect for a reason, let arrogance ignite.
Entertainment over truth, it's ignorance in the light.
Hey!
Society's in pre-bumper, don't bring Jesus each.
We celebrate the modest while intelligence betreats.
Nico answers, but we're now stupidity's the dread.
Watching as our fucker takes a nose-hit to the ass.
Hey!
Shut it down!
Headline stream with nonsense facts don't matter anymore, conspiracy theories sell well, truth gets you on the door, experts aren't discredited, one pool six and a stage, welcome to the kingdom where the jester is a sage.
We're trading wisdom for swigs, intelligence for likes.
Reading generations of minds that never think twice.
Society is a brief hop and no pancakes to seat.
We celebrate the loudest while indulging in street.
Finger, hand, cheek, bow, and house, humanity is the trend.
Once again, God contradicts, I know that to the end.
Hey!
Dumb it down!